http://museumsassn.bc.ca/british-columbia-museums-association-privacy-policy/

British Columbia Museums Association Privacy Policy - BC Museums Association
Member Log In
About UsMandate & GovernanceCouncil & CommitteesHistoryNewsSupport The BCMAContact Us Conferences BCMA BrainTools and ResourcesWebinarsRegional WorkshopsGrants and Funding OpportunitiesRoundup Grants, Awards & BursariesBursariesAwardsGrantsSponsor an AwardCriteria & Nomination MembersBecome a MemberRoundupAnnual General Meeting BC Museums & Galleries
British Columbia Museums Association Privacy PolicyCollection of Personal Information
The British Columbia Museums Association (BCMA) undertakes to collect your information by means that are fair, legal, and transparent. Personal information collected by the BCMA may include, but not be limited to, the following:
Name;
Phone number;
Email address;
Work or home address;
Credit card information – this will be collected by a third party secure site for processing.
Use of Personal Information
The BCMA collects personal information in order to:
Process purchases;
Manage registrations for conferences, workshops, annual general meetings, career development opportunities and other events;
Disseminate information regarding BCMA programs and services;
Provide members with information and benefits associated with membership.
Any other use of personal information will be subsequently agreed upon by the BCMA and the relevant parties.
Disclosure of Personal Information
BCMA employees and agents may access the information as is necessary to provide the services and opportunities as outlined in this policy.
Credit Card information is collected and processed by a third party ssl (secure sockets layer) site which has been chosen by the BCMA for its security and professionalism. However, as the BCMA does not control this site, we would encourage you to review their individual privacy policy.
Personal information will not be disclosed for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with the consent of the individual or as required by law.
Security of Personal Information
The BCMA undertakes to store your information in a manner that ensures security against unauthorized access, alteration or deletion, at a level commensurate with its sensitivity.
The BCMA periodically reviews information which is no longer required to be maintained and destroys said information.
Credit Card information disclosed on the BCMA’s website is not retained by the BCMA.
Please note that any unprotected email communication via the Internet is subject to possible loss, interception, or alteration. Consequently, we cannot and are not responsible for any damages you may suffer if you transmit personal information to us via the Internet.
The BCMA provides links to other web sites. As the BCMA does not control these sites, we would encourage you to review their individual privacy policies.
Changes to this Policy
All changes to the BCMA’s privacy policy will be posted on the BCMA website.
If you have a concern about your privacy or this policy, please contact bcma@museumsassn.bc.ca.
The BC Museums Association Secretariat is located on the traditional lands of the Songhees and Esquimalt First Nations.
We are grateful for the opportunity to live and learn here in mutual respect and appreciation.
Our Sponsors
We gratefully acknowledge the financial assistance of the Province of British Columbia
We gratefully acknowledge the generous support of the Royal BC Museum in providing a home for the BCMA secretariat.
